[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 11, "question": "What's the one piece of advice you would give any president when they walk in the Oval Office for the first time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 12, "answer": "Tell the truth.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Oval Office"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "What was the overriding concept for the center?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "Well, to promote two things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "Do you feel that you've achieved more outside of the presidency than you did when you were there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RBR", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "Well, it's a different kind of thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 62, "question": "Just on those two things alone, pretty big ticks in the box, weren't they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 63, "answer": "Well, they were.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "Did part of you celebrate and the other part slightly think, OK, what's going to happen now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "Well, both.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "Well, what should America's role be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "I think to promote democracy and freedom.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "Was that a mistake, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "I think it was a serious mistake.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 105, "question": "Do you think naturally that you are?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 106, "answer": "No, I don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "Would that be a fair comment?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "I don't think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "Do you think he means it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "I don't -- I'm not sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["House"], "LOCATION": ["Jerusalem"]}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "To the Israelis who say that you don't fully, I guess, feel their pain of being on the receiving end of the suicide bombing and the attacks and so on, what do you say to them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "DT", "NNP", "WP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "I don't have much chance to talk to Israeli leaders anymore, but last time I was over there, I did meet with the speaker of the House and I met with the deputy prime minister and also the mayor of Jerusalem.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", ",", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "Are they the people that you could have done business with as president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "Menachem Begin, when he was first elected, had a terrible reputation against peace, against any accommodation, absolutely rigid in his policies.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "Could that have happened in Iraq if it had been left to its own devices?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "Well, I certainly think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iraq"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "Is there a consistent policy that America should pursue with the three or are they all very different cases?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "CD", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "Well, they are different, but there are basic principles that should be followed.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", ":", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "Should Assad go, though, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "VB", "VB", ",", "IN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "I think Assad is likely -- very likely to go in the next few months, maybe during this current year.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "And the big question then is how does America respond if it has absolute concrete evidence that Iran now has a nuclear weapon?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "I don't think America has that kind of confidence.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "Iran"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "I mean you deliberately avoided any kind of military conflict with Iran when you were president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "Yes, I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "NN", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 218, "question": "You still think it would have been a terrible error to do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 219, "answer": "ARTER: I do, because every one of the hostages came home safe and free.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel"]}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "What would need to precipitate that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "I think a real threat against Israel, for instance, of an atomic attack, and I'm not sure that the Iranians are going toward a nuclear capability.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 238, "question": "This is an exact replica of your Oval Office, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "It is absolutely the way it was when I was president.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Oval Office"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "Same furniture?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "Same furniture, same carpet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "When you come in here, how does it make you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "It makes me feel at home.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "And Jimmy and I used to put a table between those two chairs and meet, was it every Wednesday?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "Every week.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Wednesday"], "PERSON": ["Jimmy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "I mean, you were right then and you would be right to say that today, wouldn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "So, you know, the grassroots were there, which you picked up on, but nobody listened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", ",", "CC", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "That's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "One of the questions people wanted the answers, do you actually like peanuts?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "NNS", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "I still grow peanuts, I still eat peanuts.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "You like peanuts?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "I hope everybody will join me in eating peanuts.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "Well, I think that entrepreneurial spirit was very important for me as a remote -- as a farm boy on a remote farm, who didn't know anything about the outside world, but was raised with hard work and had a nurturing parents.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"]}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "How do you think he's doing as president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "Well, he hasn't been able to accomplish very much, because he's been hamstringed by the most uncooperative Congress we've had in history, in my opinion.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "How do you personally get on with President Obama?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "We don't have any relationship much.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "Are you sad about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "I wish it was a closer relationship.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "I heard that you felt a little bit let down when the first chance he got to have you speak at a Democratic Convention, he asked you to do a documentary film instead along with President Clinton, and it was can cut from 20 minutes to four minutes, and that you were a bit cheesed off with this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "NN", "VB", "IN", "WRB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "CD", "NNS", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "Well, I was, a bit.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clinton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "Were they good reasons?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "For him to get elected, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 377, "question": "When you hear Rick Santorum using you as some stick to batter President Obama, what do you feel about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 378, "answer": "I think he's mistaken.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick Santorum", "Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "Is he meddling with the wrong guy here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "Well, I'm not dangerous to him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "Has Mitt Romney, from what you're looking at -- has he got it in the bag, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "That's the indication now.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "NNS", "RB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "When you see that kind of thing, as a very religious man yourself -- a lot of them say, look, we're very religious people; it's all in the Bible -- what do you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "I feel that they're going to extremes just to try to get votes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "And you think he's doing it deliberately?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "It's the same thing, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "Not quite.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "What's the difference?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "ARTER: Well, he's not a racist, I think.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "JJR", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "What are the warning signs for Barack Obama that you would -- if you had the chance, you would say to him, watch this, be careful about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "DT", ",", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "Well, as we mentioned on the program earlier, I think luck has a lot to do with it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "So he's never moaned again about your timekeeping?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "There's another story about him forgetting my Christmas present.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "RP", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "Sixty five year marriage -- what do you think the secret has been to the longevity of your marriage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CD", "NN", "NN", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "Well, I think maybe the hardest time we had was when he was when we came home from the White House, because it was the first time we had both been home together all day, everyday.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "Like what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "Like I want to go in my office and work without interruption.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "Who is the boss here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "He's the boss.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rosalynn"]}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "Ultimately, Rosalynn is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "Or have you just been very lucky that you've never had a period in your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "We had one time like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "ORGAN: So actually writing a book together nearly killed your marriage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "Absolutely true.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "What did you resolve from this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "We gave up our advance on the book back to our publisher.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 521, "question": "And you have never written a book again together?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 522, "answer": "Never.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "Why Guinea worms?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "It's located in very isolated villages that don't have any source of water except a pond that ponds up during the rainy season.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "How old is she now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "43.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "And whether there was a big difference?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "It's hard to go to sleep the first night, it was so excited.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 593, "question": "Are you allowed to come back?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "I think there's probably an age limit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]